<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[A glimpse into the mind of Davis Carbo]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[A glimpse into the mind of Davis Carbo]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/revolutionarysince95/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 06:26:02 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/revolutionarysince95/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Yes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Yes</h1><p>"Find a way to say yes to things"-Eric Schmidt. Saying the word "Yes" more than the word "No". Isn't it such an amazing concept, the idea of saying one word more than another and having your life change because so. I don't think I've ever taken time to say yes to every opportunity that I'm presented with. I would like to try, I'd also love it for someone to do it with me so we can compare results. Whoooos with me (this is where you start)</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/revolutionarysince95/yes/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d16da7fc-df84-45d5-8be2-e25aaa62f057</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 06:25:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome</h1><p>I'd like to thank you for coming on to my site. I have been looking for a median to express my thoughts and ideas for a while, and now that I have this site I'll be able to do so. You're welcome to stay, or go; it doesn't necessarily matter. What matters is that you understand that this is only an expression of myself, for me, and that you too should find a means of expression. I will post my thoughts, my philosophies, my lessons, my ups my downs, my stories, my memories, basically anything that comes to mind. Now that I have somewhere to bring my thoughts, I will do so openly. I hope that what I share with you will help you in some way, if it doesn't,  I suggest you find something different that can. You are in control of your life. Enjoy </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/revolutionarysince95/welcome/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f26fa126-77cd-4bc6-aa97-808c7cc5370a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 23:28:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shiloh]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Shiloh</h1><p>“Now Shiloh I don’t want you to be
nervous, but we’re going to do a little experiment; your father told me your favorite
subject at school is science, and that you’re the best at experiments”, said
Dr. Sabini as she placed a folded bandana over Shiloh’s eyes. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/revolutionarysince95/shiloh/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3d0d835e-02a7-465c-8377-9eba3c636869</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 23:07:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>